Robert Schoelkopf Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artist Files, 1851-1991, undated, Series 1:; (boxes 1-23, 23 linear ft.)
  - Tanner, Henry Ossawa, General, 1969-1987, undated (Box 19)
  - Taylor, Henry Fitch, General, 1966-1990, undated (Box 19)
  - Thayer, Abbott Handerson, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Thompson, Jerry, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Tillim, Sidney (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1969, undated (Box 19)
    - Printed Material, 1962-1977, undated (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Tomlin, Bradley Walker, General, 1970, undated (Box 19)
  - Touster, Irwin (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1972, undated, (an ink drawing dated 1963) (Box 19)
    - Printed Material, 1961-1972 (Box 19)
  - Tulk, Alfred James, Printed Material, 1974-1977, undated (Box 19)
  - Urness, Scott (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1985-1990, undated, (1 folder, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 19)
  - Urquhart, Tony, Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 19)
  - Van Everen, Jay, General, 1972, undated (Box 19)
  - Vassilief, Marie, General, 1969, undated (Box 19)
  - Vedder, Elihu, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Von Gloden, General, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Vonnoh, Robert William, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Vroman, Edward, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Walkowitz, Abraham, General, 1964, undated (Box 19)
  - Watkins, Carleton E., Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Weber, Max, General, 1955-1971, undated (Box 19)
  - Weir, Julian Alden, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Weiss, George, General, 1965-1967, undated (Box 20)
  - Whistler, James McNeill, General, 1965-1973, undated (Box 20)
  - Whittredge, Worthington, General, 1991, undated (Box 20)
  - Wiesenfeld, Paul (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1991, undated, (8 folders) (Box 20)
    - Printed Material, 1970-1991, undated (Box 20)
    - Photographs of the Artist, undated, (photograph with 3 unidentified people, possibly including Robert Schoelkopf) (Box 20)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1972-1976, undated, (2 folders, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 20)
  - Wilkins, William (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1987, undated, (4 folders) (Box 20)
    - Exhibition Lists and Résumés, 1977-1981 (Box 20)
    - Printed Material, 1977-1988 (Box 20)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1978, undated, (2 folders, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 20)
  - Wyant, Alexander H., General, 1972, undated (Box 20)
  - Wynn, Don (Box 20)
    - General, 1969-1990 (Box 20)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 20)
  - Young, Mahonri Mackintosh, General, 1958, 1963-1964, (proposals to represent Young's estate) (Box 20)
  - Zammit, Norman, General, 1962-1968, undated (Box 20)
  - Zorach, William, General, 1982, undated (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 20)
    - Unidentified Artists, 1963, undated, (3 folders) (Box 20)
    - A - F, 1968, 1975-1990, undated, (7 folders, 0.25 slide box stored at end of Box 21) (Box 20)
    - G - Z, 1955-1990, undated, (10 folders, 0.25 slide box stored at end of Box 21; letters to Bernard Rabin from Gus Mager and Robert Laurent relating to artwork by Jules Pascin in O - Q) (Box 21)
  - Additional Slide Transparencies from Series 1 (Box 21)
    - Canier, Caren (Box 21)
    - Cushing, Barbara (Box 21)
    - Dallman, Daniel (Box 21)
    - Piccolo, Richard (Box 21)
    - Roberts, Stone (Box 21)
    - Ryan, Richard (Box 21)
    - Schmidt, Edward (Box 21)
    - Sklarski, Bonnie (Box 21)
    - Stella, Joseph (Box 21)
    - Storrs, John Henry Bradley (Box 21)
    - Urness, Scott (Box 21)
    - Wiesenfeld, Paul (Box 21)
    - Wilkins, William (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, G - Z (Box 21)
  - Additional Slide Transparencies from Series 2, Artist Commissions (Box 21)
  - Negatives of Works of Art (Box 22)
    - Unidentified Artists, undated, (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Albright, Ivan - Aponovich, James, undated (Box 22)
    - Bailey, William, undated, (3 folders) (Box 22)
    - Ballaine, G. - Bell, E., undated (Box 22)
    - Bell, Leland, undated, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Bellows, George - Burra, Edward, undated (Box 22)
    - Carles, Arthur B. - Cole, Thomas, undated (Box 22)
    - Coleman, Glenn O. - Currier, [J. Frank], undated (Box 22)
    - Dallman, Daniel - Davis, Stuart, undated (Box 22)
    - Dawson, Manierre, undated (Box 22)
    - De Kooning, Willem - Duveneck, Frank, undated (Box 22)
    - Eaton - Evans, Walker, undated (Box 22)
    - Fellini - Fiske, Gertrude, undated (Box 22)
    - Flannagan, John Bernard - Frieseke, Frederick C., undated (Box 22)
    - Gallatin, A. E. - Goodwin, Arthur Clifton, undated (Box 22)
    - Gorky, Arshile - Guillaume, undated (Box 22)
    - Halsall - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, undated (Box 22)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson - Horton, William S., undated (Box 22)
    - Johnson, David - Jones, Bern, undated (Box 22)
    - Kane, John - Kline, Franz, undated (Box 22)
    - Knaths, Karl - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, undated (Box 22)
    - Lachaise, Gaston, undated, (3 folders) (Box 22)
    - Lachaise, Gaston, undated, (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Laderman, Gabriel, undated, (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Lawrence, Jacob - Luks, George, undated (Box 23)
    - MacDonald-Wright, Stanton - Martin, Homer D., undated (Box 23)
    - Matthiasdottir, Louisa, undated, (3 folders) (Box 23)
    - Matulka, Jan, undated (Box 23)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry - Mills, undated (Box 23)
    - [Morandi, Giovanni] - Myers, Jerome, undated (Box 23)
    - Nadelman, Elie - Nakian, Reuben, undated (Box 23)
    - Nevelson, Louise - Orozco, José Clemente, undated (Box 23)
    - Peterson, Jane - Pollet, Joseph, undated (Box 23)
    - Pollock, Jackson - Quin, Langdon, undated (Box 23)
    - Raiselis, Richard - [Ryder, Albert Pinkham], undated (Box 23)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus - Shaw, Sydney Dale, undated (Box 23)
    - Sheeler, Charles - Steichen, Edward, undated (Box 23)
    - Stella, Joseph, undated, (3 folders) (Box 23)
    - Storrs, John Henry Bradley, undated, (4 folders) (Box 23)
    - [Stuart, Frederick T.] - Suba, Miklos, undated (Box 23)
    - Tamayo, Rufino - Tillim, Sidney, undated (Box 23)
    - Touster, Irwin, undated (Box 23)
    - Turner, Helen - Weiss, George, undated (Box 23)
    - Whistler, James McNeill - Zorach, [William], undated (Box 23)
  - Negatives, Exhibition Files (Box 23)
    - Photographs of the American West (1985), undated (Box 23)
    - American Stone Carvers (1985), undated (Box 23)
- General Business Files, 1960-1991, undated, Series 2:; (boxes 24-28, 4.75 linear ft.)
  This series comprises records relating to the day-to-day administration of the Robert Schoelkopf Gallery. It provides extensive coverage of the gallery's relationships with a wide variety of clients including gallery owners, art dealers, museums, and art institutions primarily nationwide but also abroad. The series records activities such as appraisals; requests for information from clients and responses to their inquiries; correspondence to and from clients regarding works of art to be taken on approval or purchased; consignment of works of art; and loan arrangements.
  The largest group of files in the series contains general correspondence that provides a broad overview of business activities. These files contain the bulk of the letters offering works of art to clients and responding to requests for information, loan, or purchase. The early correspondence files in particular document how Schoelkopf actively targeted particular collectors and institutions in his efforts to launch the gallery as a going concern. The gallery maintained a group of files entitled "Correspondence-Offerings" that contained letters offering works of art to clients. However, many such letters were also contained in files labeled simply "Correspondence," and to avoid redundancy, these two sets of files were combined during processing. The first file of general correspondence contains the lease for the fourth-floor gallery space at 825 Madison Avenue.
  More detailed documentation of particular aspects of the gallery's administration can also be found in this series. Files recording appraisals contain estimates of value for works of art that Robert Schoelkopf provided to individuals for insurance purposes. Two additional files document large-scale appraisals that Schoelkopf conducted for the Art Dealers Association of America, including an appraisal of approximately two hundred works by Morgan Russell given by Henry M. Reed to the Whitney Museum of American Art.
  The gallery maintained a group of files recording works of art sent out on approval and consignment. They include incoming letters requesting loans from the gallery and replies in the form of memoranda listing works of art sent out, the terms of the loan agreement, or price of the works if purchased. During the 1970s the gallery maintained separate files for consignment of photography, and these records can be found at the end of the group. Additional records relating to photography consignment can also be found in the other approval and consignment files.
  Three files in this series document the gallery's involvement with the administration of client estates. Records relating to the estate of Arie K. Fluiter contain several pieces of correspondence with Georgia O'Keeffe discussing whether a painting owned by the Fluiter estate, Red Barn, was an early work of hers.
  This series also contains a group of files relating to individual galleries, art dealers, and clients that the gallery apparently retained for a short time. Additional records relating to these clients may be found elsewhere in the series. Arrangement of material within folders in this series is complicated by the fact that dates of final actions taken on items are often hand-written on memoranda and are later than the type-written date of the item. Generally the type-written date was taken as the primary date as this method tended to retain the original order of the material.
  - Appraisals (Box 24)
    - General, 1970-1991, (4 folders) (Box 24)
    - Art Dealers Association of America, 1980-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Approval and Consignment Records (Box 24)
    - General, 1963-1988, (15 folders) (Box 24)
    - Photography, 1969-1977, (4 folders) (Box 24)
  - Artist Commissions, 1981-1990, undated, (1 folder, 0.5 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 24)
  - Estate of Arie K. Fluiter, 1964-1980, undated (Box 24)
  - Estate of Joseph Katz, 1964-1978 (Box 24)
  - Estate of Richard Mills, 1968-1982 (correspondence with Mills) (Box 24)
  - General Correspondence, 1961-1972, undated, (26 folders) (Box 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1973-1982, (29 folders; letter from the office of the vice-president of the United States on behalf of Mrs. Walter Mondale in April 1978; correspondence with Kahlil Gibran in June-July 1979 in which Schoelkopf declines Gibran's request to deal in his sculpture and expresses his views on contemporary sculpture in general) (Box 26)
  - General Correspondence, 1983-1991, (22 folders) (Box 27)
  - General Correspondence, Photography, 1963-1974, undated, (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - General Correspondence, Photography, 1975-1978, 1984-1989, (3 folders) (Box 28)
  - Gifts from Martin Horowitz, 1970-1976, undated, (gifts to various institutions handled by the gallery) (Box 28)
  - Gifts from Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, 1981-1985 (Box 28)
  - Individual Galleries and Clients (Box 28)
    - D'Offay Couper Gallery, 1971-1980, undated (Box 28)
    - Fader, Jack, 1972-1978 (Box 28)
    - Fust, John, 1962-1970, undated (Box 28)
    - Graphics International, Ltd., 1973-1980, undated, (correspondence with Harry H. Lunn, Jr.) (Box 28)
    - Halsted 831 Gallery, 1971-1975, undated (Box 28)
    - James Goodman Gallery, 1962-1967, undated (Box 28)
    - Maxwell Galleries, Ltd., 1958-1965 (Box 28)
    - Millard, Charles, 1973-1976 (Box 28)
    - Neumann, Elsa Schmidt, 1962-1967 (Box 28)
    - R. E. Lewis, Inc., 1962-1967 (Box 28)
    - Rabin, Bernard, 1973-1984 (Box 28)
    - Strauser, Sterling, 1963-1977, (letter describing meeting Justin McCarthy for the first time) (Box 28)
    - Terry DeLapp Gallery, 1962-1967, undated (Box 28)
    - Wilmerding, John, 1973, undated (Box 28)
  - Inventory Purchases (Box 28)
    - General, 1960-1973, 1984, (3 folders) (Box 28)
    - Photography, 1972-1976, undated, (3 folders) (Box 28)
  - Legal Records, 1966-1982, undated (Box 28)
  - Photograph Catalogue, undated, (compilation of gallery catalog) (Box 28)
  - Photography, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 28)
  - Restoration of Works of Art, 1978-1990, undated (Box 28)
  - Works Offered to Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, 1972-1984, undated (Box 28)
- Group Exhibition Files, 1960-1988, undated, Series 3:; (boxes 28-29, 1 linear ft.)
  This series primarily documents group exhibitions held at the Robert Schoelkopf Gallery between 1963 and 1987, in addition to several exhibitions held in other locations. Records relating to exhibitions of work by individual artists are not included in this series but can be found in Series 1: Aftist Files. The first files in the series contain exhibition lists and printed material for shows that have no accompanying material and thus are not represented in an individual folder. Much of the printed matter consists of general reference material relating to themes of group shows held at the gallery. It also documents group exhibitions at other locations that featured artists in whom the gallery had an interest. Three folders of photographs that were originally labeled "Publicity Photographs" can be found immediately following these files.
  The bulk of the series deals with specific exhibitions. Records include photographs of installations and individual works of art shown, exhibition catlogs, clippings, press releases, and material pertaining to related events. Correspondence concerning arrangements for exhibitions and requests for information can also be found here. Files chronicling specific exhibitions are arranged chronologically, with the exception of three files combining material relating to two exhibitions entitled Nine Realist Painters and Nine Realist Painters Revisited that can be found at the end of the series. Dates of exhibitions are given in parentheses after the exhibition titles and should not be confused with record dates.
  The series contains ten negatives of photographs used in the 1985 exhibition, Photographs of the American West, and three negatives of installation shots from the 1985 exhibition, American Stone Carvers. For preservation reasons these are stored at the end of the negatives from Series 1: Artist Files, in Box 24.
  A list of all known exhibitions held at the gallery, both one-person and group shows, is available as an appendix
  - Exhibition Lists, 1967-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Printed Material, 1962-1988, undated, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Photography Exhibitions, Publicity Photographs, undated, (3 folders) (Box 28)
  - Naive Art of the World (1961), General, 1960-1961, undated (Box 28)
  - 19th Century American Paintings (1963), General, 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - New York, New York (1964), General, 1957, 1964 (Box 28)
  - 19th & 20th Century Americans (1965), General, 1965 (Box 28)
  - 19th & 20th Century American Paintings (1967), General, 1967 (Box 28)
  - Significant 19th and 20th Century Photographs (1970), General, 1970 (Box 28)
  - Brooklyn Bridge (1973) (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1974, undated, (illustrated postcard from Paul Katz) (Box 28)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1973, 1983, undated (Box 28)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1972-1973, 1983, undated (Box 28)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated, (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Photography in Italy in the Nineteenth Century (1973-1974), General, 1973 (Box 29)
  - The Art of the Portrait Photograph (1974) (Box 29)
    - General, 1970-1974 (Box 29)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 29)
  - Four Americans (1975), General, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Altar Pieces of World War II (1975) (Box 29)
    - General, 1975-1980, undated (Box 29)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated, (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - New Talent (1975), General, 1975-1977, undated (Box 29)
  - Cyanotypes by Well-Known and Amateur Photographers from the Turn of the Century and Today (1976), General, 1976, undated (Box 29)
  - Drawings by Gallery Artists (1976), General, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Brooklyn College Art Department Past and Present, 1942-1977 1977) (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1977, undated (Box 29)
    - Printed Material, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 29)
  - Early 20th Century American Modernist Painting (1978), General, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Emile Branchard and William Fellini: Two 20th Century American Primitive Painters (1978), General, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Artists' Choice Exhibition (1979), Correspondence, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Contemporary Arcadian Paintings (1982), General, 1982-1983, undated (Box 29)
  - Recent American Still Life Painting (1984), General, 1984, undated (Box 29)
  - American Wood Carvers of the 19th and 20th Centuries 1985) (Box 29)
    - General, 1979-1985 (Box 29)
    - Photograph of Installations, 1978 (Box 29)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 29)
  - Recent American Portraiture (1985), General, undated (Box 29)
  - Photographs of the American West (1985) (Box 29)
    - General, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, undated, (filed in Box 24) (Box 29)
  - American Stone Carvers (1985) (Box 29)
    - General, 1985-1986, undated (Box 29)
    - Photographs of Installations, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 29)
    - Negatives of Installations, 1985, filed in Box 24) (Box 29)
  - City Streets (1986), General, 1962-1986, undated (Box 29)
  - The Figure: American Sculpture of the Early 20th Century (1988), General, 1988, undated (Box 29)
  - Nine Realist Painters (1963-1964), Nine Realist Painters Revisited (1984-1985) (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1985, undated (Box 29)
    - Printed Material, 1964-1985 (Box 29)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 29)
- Photographs of Artists, 1963-1981, undated, Series 4:; (box 29, 0.25 ft.)
  This series comprises a group of photographs and slide transparencies of artists stored separately by the Robert Schoelkopf Gallery from other photographs of artists that are interspersed throughout the collection. The majority of the images are of artists whose work the gallery did not handle. They are arranged alphabetically by artist, with unidentified artists placed at the beginning of the group.
  - Unidentified Artists, undated, (4 folders) (Box 29)
  - Bishop, Isabel, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Bomar, Bill, 1978, (taken 1966) (Box 29)
  - Burlin, Paul, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Cavallon, Georgio, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Citron, Minna Wright, 1981 (Box 29)
  - de Graf, José, 1976 (Box 29)
  - De Kooning, Willem, 1976, undated (Box 29)
  - Delevante, Sidney, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Dickinson, Edwin Walter, 1978, (taken 1966) (Box 29)
  - [Ether], Curtis, 1974 (Box 29)
  - Giobbi, Edward, 1978, (taken 1964) (Box 29)
  - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Gross, Chaim, 1978, (taken 1963) (Box 29)
  - Kiesler, Frederick, 1974, 1978, (taken 1965) (Box 29)
  - Kroll, Leon, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Marcks, Gerhard, undated (Box 29)
  - Marcus, Maria, 1978, undated (Box 29)
  - Michael, Lily, undated (Box 29)
  - Morrison, George, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Motherwell, Robert, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Nevelson, Louise, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Ortiz, Rafael Montanez, 1978, undated (Box 29)
  - [Pierce, Margy], undated (Box 29)
  - Romano, Claudia, undated (Box 29)
  - Roose, Roselyn, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Rothko, Mark, 1978, undated, (taken 1965) (Box 29)
  - Segal, George, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Shaier, Mary, 1978, undated (Box 29)
  - Sievan, Maurice, 1978, undated (Box 29)
  - Smith, David, undated (Box 29)
  - Soyer, Moses, 1978, (taken 1963) (Box 29)
  - Soyer, Raphael, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Tworkow, Jack, 1978, undated (Box 29)
  - Vincente, Esteban, 1976, undated (Box 29)
  - Warhol, Andy, undated (Box 29)
Index 2: List of Exhibitions at Robert Schoelkopf Gallery
Below is a list of all known exhibitions held at the Robert Schoelkopf Gallery. Italics indicate that the exact title of an exhibition is is known. Brackets indicate that the date or occurrence of an exhibition is assumed but cannot be confirmed.
Date Exhibition
Nov., 1962 A Selection of Drawings & Watercolors
Nov. 13-Dec. 1, 1962 Johan Birnie
Dec. 4-22, 1962 Norman Zammitt
Jan. 2-Feb. 9, 1963 Joseph Stella
Mar. 5-30, 1963 19th Century American Paintings
Apr. 2-27, 1963 Ethel Myers: Drawings and Sculpture
May 1-31, 1963 Gus Mager (1878-1955)
Oct. 1-19, 1963 Murray Reich: Recent Paintings
Oct. 19-Nov. 16, 1963 Joseph Stella
Nov. 9-Dec. 7, 1963 Irwin Touster
Dec. 10-Jan. 4, 1964 9 Realist Painters
Jan. 7-25, 1964 19th Century American Paintings & Drawings: Beckwith, Bierstadt, Bradford, Carlsen, Chase, Cropsey, Durand, Duveneck, Field, Gifford, Kensett, Harnett, Hassam, La Farge, Leavitt, Martin, Melchers, Moran, Ranger, Ream, Richards, Stella
Jan. 28-Feb. 15, 1964 Louisa Matthiasdottir: Recent Paintings
Feb. 18-Mar. 14, 1964 An Exhibition of Portraits by Gaston Lachaise
Mar.-Apr., 1964 Joseph Pollet
May 5-30, 1964 Antonio Salemme
June 2-26, 1964 New York, New York
Oct., 1964 Joseph Stella: An Exhibition of Drawings
[Nov.], 1964 [Gabriel Laderman]
undated, 1965 Lisa Muller
Jan. 5-30, 1965 Lillian Delevoryas
Mar. 2-27, 1965 Sidney Tillim
Apr., 1965 Joseph Pollet
May, 1965 George Weiss
May 25-June 25, 1965 19th and 20th Century Americans
Oct. 26-Nov. 13, 1965 Joseph Fiore
Dec. 7-31, 1965 George Bentley Nick
Jan. 4-29, 1966 Robert Cornell Memorial Exhibition
Jan. 11-29, 1966 Douglas Gorsline
Feb. 1-19, 1966 Drawings and Sculpture by Gaston Lachaise
Feb. 23-Mar. 13, 1966 Leland Bell: Paintings
Mar.-Apr., 1966 Charles Marks: Drawings
Mar. 15-Apr. 2, 1966 Ethel Myers
Apr. 5-23, 1966 Louisa Matthiasdottir
Apr. 26-May 14, 1966 Joseph Cornell: Collages
May 17-June 11, 1966 Lillian Delevoryas
July 1-31, 1966 A Selection of Modern Sculpture: Becquet, Bolotowsky, Butler, Calder, Chadwick, Dalou, Davidson, Flannagan, Gauguin, Kogan, Kuhn, Lachaise, Manzu, Marini, Moore, Nadelman, Rodin, Salemme
Oct. 11-29, 1966 Adolph Rosenblatt
Nov. 1-19, 1966 Joseph Stella: Watercolors, Drawings, and Collages
Nov. 22-Dec. 10, 1966 Sydney Dale Shaw
Dec. 20-Jan. 7, 1967 Walker Evans
Jan. 10-Feb. 4, 1967 Miklos Suba
Feb. 7-25, 1967 Joseph Pollet: Paris, Seven Years
Feb.-Mar., 1967 Charles Marks: Paintings, 1960-1967
Mar. 21-Apr. 8, 1967 19th & 20th Century American Paintings
Apr. 11-29, 1967 Gabriel Laderman: Recent Paintings
May 2-20, 1967 Recent Paintings and Watercolors by Sidney Tillim
May 23-July 28, 1967 19th and 20th Century American Landscapes
Sept. 19-Oct. 7, 1967 Exhibition of Watercolors, Drawings and Prints by Gallery Artists
Sept. 19-Oct. 7, 1967 Sculpture by Thyra Davidson
Oct. 10-31, 1967 George Bentley Nick: Recent Paintings
Oct. 31-Nov. 25, 1967 Figurative Painting of the Fifties
Nov., 1967 19th & 20th Century American Art
Nov. 28-Jan. 6, 1968 Julia Margaret Cameron, 1815-1879
Jan. 9-27, 1968 Louisa Matthiasdottir: Paintings and Sculpture
Jan. 30-Feb. 17, 1968 William Bailey
Mar. 19-Apr. 13, 1968 Jane Peterson: Paintings, 1910-1920
Apr. 16-May 4, 1968 Leland Bell: Paintings
May 7-31, 1968 Yun Gee
Sept. 28-Oct. 17, 1968 Leonard Leibowitz: Paintings and Etchings
Oct. 19-Nov. 7, 1968 Adolph Rosenblatt
Nov. 9-Dec. 5, 1968 Louise Kruger
Nov. 22.-Dec. 10, 1968 Sydney Dale Shaw
Dec. 7-Jan. 2, 1969 Gertrude Fiske: Oil Paintings, 1910-1928
Jan. 4-23, 1969 Irwin Touster
Jan. 25-Feb. 13, 1969 Joseph Fiore: Recent Paintings
Feb. 15-Mar. 6, 1969 William S. Horton